Guide to the J. J. Darrow diaries, 1885-1924
Darrow, J. J. diaries, 1885-1924
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
J. J. Darrow diaries, 1885-1924
4431
J. J. Darrow
25 v.
Diaries.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Farm diaries.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Farm diaries.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Darrow, J. J.
Subjects:
Farms--New York (State)--West Eaton.; Farmers.
Places:
Madison County (N.Y.)--Social life and customs.; West Eaton (N.Y.)--Commerce.
Form and Genre Terms:
Diaries.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- 1885 (Box 1)
- 1889 (Box 1)
- 1893 (Box 1)
- 1896 (Box 1)
- 1898 (Box 1)
- 1899 (Box 1)
- 1901-1906 (Box 1)
- 1908 (Box 1)
- 1909 (Box 1)
- 1911-1917 (Box 1)
- 1920-1922 (Box 1)
- 1924 (Box 1)